<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Road Safety &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<atom:link href="/https://www.chaibasa.org/tag/road-safety/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<description>Chaibasa is a town and a municipality in West Singhbhum district in the state of Jharkhand, India.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 20:48:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>/https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/cropped-abc1-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Road Safety &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<link>/https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>35 people fined in 2 days, recovered 60 thousand</title>
		<link>/https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/02/35-people-fined-in-2-days-recovered-60-thousand</link>
					<comments>/https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/02/35-people-fined-in-2-days-recovered-60-thousand#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 20:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[City Services]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Safety]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=463</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The District Transport Department has imposed a total fine of 60 thousand rupees on 33 motorcycles and 2 Tata Magic drivers for violating traffic rules within two days. In Chaibasa, a motorcycle driver incurred a total loss of six thousand rupees due to lack of license and helmet. On behalf of the District Transport Department, &#8230; <a href="/https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/02/35-people-fined-in-2-days-recovered-60-thousand" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "35 people fined in 2 days, recovered 60 thousand"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="650" height="508" src="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/chaibasa-challan.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-464" srcset="/https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/chaibasa-challan.jpg 650w, /https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/chaibasa-challan-300x234.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 709px) 85vw, (max-width: 909px) 67vw, (max-width: 984px) 61vw, (max-width: 1362px) 45vw, 600px" /><figcaption>Motorcyclists without helmet fined by Chaibsasa Transport Department. </figcaption></figure>



<p>The District Transport Department has imposed a total fine of 60 thousand rupees on 33 motorcycles and 2 Tata Magic drivers for violating traffic rules within two days. In Chaibasa, a motorcycle driver incurred a total loss of six thousand rupees due to lack of license and helmet.</p>



<p> On behalf of the District Transport Department, it was told that on Wednesday, by running a motorcycle investigation campaign in front of the Sadar police station, 11 motorcyclists without helmets were charged a total penalty of Rs 11 thousand. </p>



<p>Similarly, motorists were checked without a helmet in front of Mufassil police station on Tuesday. During this period, a fine of Rs 49 thousand was recovered from 22 motorcycle drivers and two Tata Magic drivers. Tata Magic was from Odisha and did not have permits here. 10–10 thousand rupees were recovered from both. </p>



<p>Here, Inspector cum Sadar police station in-charge Niranjan Tiwari said that the motorists would be constantly monitored. Most people ride their bikes without helmets. The police will keep a special watch on these. Also, youth and women below the age of 18 years will also be monitored. </p>



<p>Younger young men and women will be stopped first, after which their family members will be called and fined. Special attention will be paid to this. In most of the road accidents that are happening right now, girls learning scooty are involved, three people sit and ride while learning.</p>



<p> Police do not mean to harass anyone. Police ask people to wear helmets continuously for the safety of the motorcycle and scooty drivers. If you are wearing a helmet, then the police have no problem. Niranjan Tiwari called upon the motorcycle driver not to drive without a helmet and go safely to his home.</p>



<p>Also see: &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/12/workers-stopped-construction-of-chaibasa-medical-college">Medical School in Chaibasa</a></p>



<p> Follow us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook </a>and <a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a> </p>



<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-chalan-kata-20003375.html">Jagran</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/02/35-people-fined-in-2-days-recovered-60-thousand/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Road Safety</title>
		<link>/https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety</link>
					<comments>/https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Safety]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The monthly meeting of the Road Safety Committee was held on Tuesday. It was held under the chairmanship of Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal. In the meeting, the Deputy Commissioner directed the executive engineer of National Highway to apply road signs in Jhinkpani-Hattgamaharia and Hattgamaharia-Jaitgarh Road. He also mentioned filling the potholes located in National Highways, &#8230; <a href="/https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Road Safety"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The monthly meeting of the Road Safety Committee was held on Tuesday. It was held under the chairmanship of Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal. In the meeting, the Deputy Commissioner directed the executive engineer of National Highway to apply road signs in Jhinkpani-Hattgamaharia and Hattgamaharia-Jaitgarh Road. He also mentioned filling the potholes located in National Highways, and widening the roadside along Bandgaon. </p>



<p>The Deputy Commissioner also mentioned that now two thousand fine will be charged for vehicles parked on the roadside. On the other hand, eye check-up camp will be organized for the drivers of heavy vehicles. He further added that the new Trauma Center will be constructed shortly for the cost of 1 crore and 20 lakh by the Uranium Corporation Limited.</p>



<p> At the same time, a rural road safety committee will be constituted at the Panchayat level, in which social people will be added so that they can immediately assist the injured people in road accidents.</p>



<p>Superintendent of Police Indrajit Martha instructed the police stations to conduct helmets and vehicle checks in all the places extensively to prevent major road accidents and injuries. The overloaded vehicles will also be examined strictly.</p>



<p> Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Also see &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/joda-talab-to-be-renovated">Joda Talab to be renovated.</a></p>



<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-dc-meeting-news-19343801.html">Jagran</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
