<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Community Hall &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.chaibasa.org/tag/community-hall/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<description>Chaibasa is a town and a municipality in West Singhbhum district in the state of Jharkhand, India.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:38:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/cropped-abc1-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Community Hall &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<link>https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>New Community Hall in Gandhi Tola</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Community Hall]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gandhi Tola]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The people of Gandhi Tola, Chaibasa will not have to wander around for marriage and other small programs. For this, a community building will be constructed at the cost of Rs 8,30,600, right next to the Shree Shree Durga Puja Mandap Gandhi Tola. This community building will be made from the fund of the JMM &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "New Community Hall in Gandhi Tola"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The people of Gandhi Tola, Chaibasa will not have to wander around for marriage and other small programs. For this, a community building will be constructed at the cost of Rs 8,30,600, right next to the Shree Shree Durga Puja Mandap Gandhi Tola. This community building will be made from the fund of the JMM legislator Deepak Biruva. </p>



<p>There will be a hall, a balcony, a room, and a toilet in the arranged fashion. On this matter, MLA Deepak Biruwa laid the foundation stone for the construction of a community building with duly worshiping the God and the Goddess. He addressed the people of Gandhi Tola on this occasion and said that it was an old demand of the people here that due to lack of community building in Gandhi Tola there was a problem of marriage and other small programs of the community. </p>



<p>The MLA told the contractor that the community building should be completed within the time limit. There will be no compromise on the quality of the hall during construction. On this occasion Chaibasa Chamber cum Chairman of Shree Shree Gandhi Tola Durga Puja Pandal Committee, Nitin Prakash, Ghanshyam Darbara, Vilas Roy, Mukhiya Sumitra Devgam, Dumbishai Manaki Dalpati Devgam, Ashutosh Kumar alias Chhotu, Neeraj Kumar, TK Raj Mohan, Ravi Prasad, Avinash Yadav, Shubham Sinha , Utpal Gopalan, Shashi Prasad, Ratna Sinha, R Border, Anita Roy, Usha Singh, Shobha Sinha, Baby Devi etc. were present.</p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-samudaik-bhawan-19358475.html">Jagran</a></p>



<p>Also see &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/uninterrupted-power-supply">Uninterrupted Power Supply in Chaibasa</a></p>



<p>

Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
