<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorised &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.chaibasa.org/category/uncategorised/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<description>Chaibasa is a town and a municipality in West Singhbhum district in the state of Jharkhand, India.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 17:43:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/cropped-abc1-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Uncategorised &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<link>https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Free Coaching Center opened in Gutusai, Chaibasa</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/10/free-coaching-center-opened-in-gutusai-chaibasa</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/10/free-coaching-center-opened-in-gutusai-chaibasa#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 17:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=499</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Free coaching center was inaugurated on Sunday for the preparation of Navodaya and Netarhat in Gutusai with the untiring efforts of Helping Hand Chaibasa. Neha Nishad, founder of Helping Hand Chaibasa, said that during the early times of lockdown when she was distributing rice and food to the poor and needy people in the street, &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/10/free-coaching-center-opened-in-gutusai-chaibasa" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Free Coaching Center opened in Gutusai, Chaibasa"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="650" height="301" src="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/Helping-Hand-Chaibasa-1.jpg" alt="Helping Hand, Chaibasa team with children" class="wp-image-501" srcset="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/Helping-Hand-Chaibasa-1.jpg 650w, https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2020/10/Helping-Hand-Chaibasa-1-300x139.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 709px) 85vw, (max-width: 909px) 67vw, (max-width: 984px) 61vw, (max-width: 1362px) 45vw, 600px" /><figcaption>Helping Hand, Chaibasa team with children</figcaption></figure>



<p>Free coaching center was inaugurated on Sunday for the preparation of Navodaya and Netarhat in Gutusai with the untiring efforts of Helping Hand Chaibasa. </p>



<p>Neha Nishad, founder of Helping Hand Chaibasa, said that during the early times of lockdown when she was distributing rice and food to the poor and needy people in the street, she got many children who have left their schooling completely. After leaving studies, children were wandering here and there and adopting wrong habits. </p>



<p>Neha along with her group searched for such children who needed education enrolled them in school. She and her group are teaching these children. Thinking that the future of these children should be bright, Neha thought of running a free coaching institute for the preparation of Navodaya and Netarhat, and did that work today. </p>



<p>Vikas Dodrajka, Sanjay Kachhap, Prakash Laguri, Arvid Laguri and Engineer Amrit etc. were present at the inauguration ceremony of the institute. The Helping Hand team guided the children about their future and said that they will always be ready to serve and help them. </p>



<p>Meanwhile, the children present here also presented a sample of their talent. Here, a nine year old child, Lakshya Laguri, was the center of attention, having won the gold by defeating the Australian player in Taekkond a year earlier. He also talked about coming to coaching institute to study for the preparation of Netarhat. Other members of Helping Hands Chaibasa were Poonam Jha, Gudiya Rajak, Sudhanshu Shekhar, Kapil Chirania, Sonu Kumar, Manish Nishad, Adil and Amit etc. on the occasion. As well as a group of 35 children were also present there.</p>



<p></p>



<p>Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-chaibasa-free-coaching-news-20833963.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Jagran</a></p>



<p>Also Read &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/04/fight-against-coronavirus-in-west-singhbhum">Fight Against Coronavirus in West Singhbhum</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2020/10/free-coaching-center-opened-in-gutusai-chaibasa/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Painting, General Knowledge and Science Competition</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/painting-general-knowledge-and-science-competition</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/painting-general-knowledge-and-science-competition#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2019 13:45:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Painting Competition]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Science Competition]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=436</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[6th Inter-School Painting, General Knowledge and Science Competition is being organized by the Gaints Group of Chaibasa and sponsored by &#8216;Satyam Builders&#8217;, under the &#8216;Knowledge-Campaign 2019&#8217; program, on August 4 (Sunday) at local Padmavati Jain Saraswati Shishu Vidya Mandir in Chaibasa Like every year, this painting contest is for students from class LKG to class &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/painting-general-knowledge-and-science-competition" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Painting, General Knowledge and Science Competition"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>6th Inter-School Painting, General Knowledge and Science Competition is  <br>being organized by the Gaints Group of Chaibasa and sponsored by &#8216;Satyam Builders&#8217;, under the &#8216;Knowledge-Campaign 2019&#8217; program,  on August 4 (Sunday) at local Padmavati Jain Saraswati Shishu Vidya Mandir in Chaibasa </p>



<p>Like every year, this painting contest is for students from class LKG to class 10th, general knowledge competition is for students from class 5th to 10th and science competition is for students from class 7th to 10th.</p>



<p>Details for painting competition &#8211; </p>



<p>Class &#8211; Timings &#8211;  Topic</p>



<ul><li>Class LKG and UKG &#8211; 9 am to 10 am &#8211; Fill colors in the given picture.</li><li>Class 1 and 2 &#8211; 9 am to 10 pm &#8211; Make a picture of a fish and fill the color.</li><li>Class 3 and 4  &#8211; 11.30 am to 12.30 am &#8211; Make a picture of the boat in the water and fill the color.</li><li>Class 5 and 6 &#8211; 11.30 am to 12.30 pm &#8211; Make a picture of a flower with leaves.</li><li>Class 7 and 8 &#8211; 1.30 pm to 2.30 pm &#8211; Make a picture of Shaheed Bhagat Singh.</li><li>Class 9 and 10 &#8211; 1.30 pm to 2.30 pm &#8211; Describe your school premises.</li></ul>



<p>Detailed information regarding the program has been made available to all schools. In order to facilitate the students, apart from schools. Registration for drawing and general knowledge competition can be done at various places in Chaibasa. The registration fee is only 30 rupees.</p>



<p>The science competition will be held in two groups for class 7th-8th and 9th-10th. Up to two entries per group will be accepted from each school in the competition. Only the selected students/students selected by the school will be able to participate in the competition and the registration fee for this contest is only Rs.100 / &#8211; per group. This competition will be held from 2 pm to 5 pm in Madhav Auditorium.</p>



<p> The result of the competition and the prize distribution ceremony will be held on August 25 at 4.30 pm in Mangilal Rungta Plus 2 School Chaibasa.</p>



<p>Also, see &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/district-athletic-championship">District Athletic Championship</a></p>



<p> Follow us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook </a>and <a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-education-19449389.html">Jagran</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/painting-general-knowledge-and-science-competition/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>District Athletic Championship</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/district-athletic-championship</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/district-athletic-championship#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 18:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[athletics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[sports]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=429</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On the 27th and 28th of July, the West Singhbhum District Athletics Championship will be held in Zila School Ground. General secretary of West Singhbhum District Athletics Association Ajay Kumar Nayak told that participants from different age groups can participate in this competition. Participants can participate in various categories of under-12 boys and girls, under &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/district-athletic-championship" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "District Athletic Championship"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>On the 27th and 28th of July, the West Singhbhum District Athletics Championship will be held in Zila School Ground. General secretary of West Singhbhum District Athletics Association Ajay Kumar Nayak told that participants from different age groups can participate in this competition. </p>



<p>Participants can participate in various categories of under-12 boys and girls, under 14 boys and girls, under 16 boys and girls, under 18 boys and girls, under 20 boys and girls and men and women&#8217;s events. In this competition, there will be events of 100m, 200m, 400m, 800m, 1500m race, long jumping, disk throws, etc. Interested Participants can contact the Association&#8217;s office for name registration in the event.</p>



<p>Also see:- <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/jal-shakti-abhiyan-and-plantation">Jal Shakti Abhiyan</a></p>



<p>Follow us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Source:- <a href="https://www.bhaskar.com/jharkhand/chaibasa/news/district-athletic-championships-in-chaibasa-from-july-27-084506-5063758.html">Bhaskar</a></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/district-athletic-championship/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jal Shakti Abhiyan and Plantation</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/jal-shakti-abhiyan-and-plantation</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/jal-shakti-abhiyan-and-plantation#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2019 18:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chaibasa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Jal Shakti Abhiyan]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Plantation]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=416</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Water, forest and land have always been the first priority for the people of Jharkhand. Kolhan Division is particularly known for its water, forest, and land. Now, when the government launched a Jal Shakti Abhiyan and started a big scale plantation program. So the people of Kolhan are not only welcoming the initiative of the &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/jal-shakti-abhiyan-and-plantation" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Jal Shakti Abhiyan and Plantation"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Water, forest and land have always been the first priority for the people of Jharkhand. Kolhan Division is particularly known for its water, forest, and land. Now, when the government launched a <strong>Jal Shakti Abhiyan</strong> and started a big scale plantation program. So the people of Kolhan are not only welcoming the initiative of the central government but have joined in to save water and forests.</p>



<p>The MPs of the Opposition party are also openly praising the central government&#8217;s <strong>Jal Shakti Abhiyan</strong> and campaign to plant trees on large scale. The river festival organized by the Chaibasa Forest Division on the banks of the Kuju river of Chaibasa and the plantation program was inaugurated by Congress MP Geeta Koda and JMM MLA Deepak Birua by planting trees.</p>



<p>On this occasion, SP Inderjit Mehta, the leaders of various political parties, workers, forest department and officers of CRPF, school children planted trees. While addressing the river festival, Congress MP Geeta Koda appreciated this initiative of the government and said that there is a need for a mass movement to save water and forests.</p>



<p>Everyone should be connected to it, it is not possible to preserve water until the trees are formed. That is why the government&#8217;s program of plantation along river banks is commendable. JMM legislator Deepak Birua also lauded the government&#8217;s initiative and said that JMM&#8217;s slogan is saving the forest, forest, and land. That&#8217;s why we are all in this initiative of the government. The MLA said that if we do not save the Jungle, the next generation will also have to buy water.</p>



<p>Also see &#8211;  <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola">New Community Hall in Chaibasa</a></p>



<p> Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://zeenews.india.com/hindi/india/bihar-jharkhand/government-started-jal-shakti-abhiyan-plantation-started-in-chaibasa/551635">ZeeNews</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/jal-shakti-abhiyan-and-plantation/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>New Community Hall in Gandhi Tola</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 17:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Community Hall]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gandhi Tola]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=406</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The people of Gandhi Tola, Chaibasa will not have to wander around for marriage and other small programs. For this, a community building will be constructed at the cost of Rs 8,30,600, right next to the Shree Shree Durga Puja Mandap Gandhi Tola. This community building will be made from the fund of the JMM &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "New Community Hall in Gandhi Tola"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The people of Gandhi Tola, Chaibasa will not have to wander around for marriage and other small programs. For this, a community building will be constructed at the cost of Rs 8,30,600, right next to the Shree Shree Durga Puja Mandap Gandhi Tola. This community building will be made from the fund of the JMM legislator Deepak Biruva. </p>



<p>There will be a hall, a balcony, a room, and a toilet in the arranged fashion. On this matter, MLA Deepak Biruwa laid the foundation stone for the construction of a community building with duly worshiping the God and the Goddess. He addressed the people of Gandhi Tola on this occasion and said that it was an old demand of the people here that due to lack of community building in Gandhi Tola there was a problem of marriage and other small programs of the community. </p>



<p>The MLA told the contractor that the community building should be completed within the time limit. There will be no compromise on the quality of the hall during construction. On this occasion Chaibasa Chamber cum Chairman of Shree Shree Gandhi Tola Durga Puja Pandal Committee, Nitin Prakash, Ghanshyam Darbara, Vilas Roy, Mukhiya Sumitra Devgam, Dumbishai Manaki Dalpati Devgam, Ashutosh Kumar alias Chhotu, Neeraj Kumar, TK Raj Mohan, Ravi Prasad, Avinash Yadav, Shubham Sinha , Utpal Gopalan, Shashi Prasad, Ratna Sinha, R Border, Anita Roy, Usha Singh, Shobha Sinha, Baby Devi etc. were present.</p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-samudaik-bhawan-19358475.html">Jagran</a></p>



<p>Also see &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/uninterrupted-power-supply">Uninterrupted Power Supply in Chaibasa</a></p>



<p>

Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/07/new-community-hall-in-gandhi-tola/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Uninterrupted Power Supply</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/uninterrupted-power-supply</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/uninterrupted-power-supply#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 13:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Power Supply]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=397</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Rahul Purvar, MD of Jharkhand Bijli Vitran Nigam Limited(JBVNL) reviewed the various works being done by the Department of Electricity in the division on Wednesday. After this, he said that the power system of Chaibasa and Chakradharpur will be rectified by October. He also mentioned that the uninterrupted power supply will be restored in both &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/uninterrupted-power-supply" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Uninterrupted Power Supply"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Rahul Purvar, MD of Jharkhand Bijli Vitran Nigam Limited(JBVNL) reviewed the various works being done by the Department of Electricity in the division on Wednesday. After this, he said that the power system of Chaibasa and Chakradharpur will be rectified by October. He also mentioned that the uninterrupted power supply will be restored in both Chaibasa and Chakradharpur as well as in rural areas. </p>



<p>In the review, the GM of the Electricity Department and the Chief of the Engineer and other senior officials of Chaibasa-Chakradharpur and Jamshedpur Department were present. Rahul Purvar informed the people that 20 new power substations are being constructed for the uninterrupted power supply so that there is no problem of power cuts in the upcoming electricity. </p>



<p>The rigging system is being brought in so that if a power line from one grid to the substation is interrupted, then the power can be supplied by connecting with the second grid. Then, there will be no problem of power cuts in the city and rural areas. Due to the excessive power supply, there will be less loss in the electric department. He said that now the loss of the department is 22 percent. Work is being done to reduce it to 15 percent. Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal was also present on the occasion.</p>



<h3>Schemes running in the district &#8211; </h3>



<ul><li>In the important urban areas of Chaibasa around 4.5 to 5 km, the underground will be done with 11 thousand KVA wire </li><li>Old 33 KVA wire will be replaced with new ones.</li><li>Two grids will be constructed in Naomundi and Chakradharpur.</li><li>By 15th August, every house will have an electric meter.</li><li>20 new power sub-stations are being constructed to ensure uninterrupted power supply in rural areas.</li><li>All villages of the Gudari block are being worked for power supply.</li><li>The department is working to ensure a 100% electricity supply by removing the faults and the imperfections.</li><li>The Polymer AV switch will be installed in the power station so that power cuts are reduced and people get better results.</li></ul>



<p>Also see &#8211;<a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety"> Road Safety in Chaibasa</a></p>



<p>Follow us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-electrc-dept-meeting-19346565.html">Jagran</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/uninterrupted-power-supply/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Road Safety</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 15:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Road Safety]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=392</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The monthly meeting of the Road Safety Committee was held on Tuesday. It was held under the chairmanship of Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal. In the meeting, the Deputy Commissioner directed the executive engineer of National Highway to apply road signs in Jhinkpani-Hattgamaharia and Hattgamaharia-Jaitgarh Road. He also mentioned filling the potholes located in National Highways, &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Road Safety"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The monthly meeting of the Road Safety Committee was held on Tuesday. It was held under the chairmanship of Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal. In the meeting, the Deputy Commissioner directed the executive engineer of National Highway to apply road signs in Jhinkpani-Hattgamaharia and Hattgamaharia-Jaitgarh Road. He also mentioned filling the potholes located in National Highways, and widening the roadside along Bandgaon. </p>



<p>The Deputy Commissioner also mentioned that now two thousand fine will be charged for vehicles parked on the roadside. On the other hand, eye check-up camp will be organized for the drivers of heavy vehicles. He further added that the new Trauma Center will be constructed shortly for the cost of 1 crore and 20 lakh by the Uranium Corporation Limited.</p>



<p> At the same time, a rural road safety committee will be constituted at the Panchayat level, in which social people will be added so that they can immediately assist the injured people in road accidents.</p>



<p>Superintendent of Police Indrajit Martha instructed the police stations to conduct helmets and vehicle checks in all the places extensively to prevent major road accidents and injuries. The overloaded vehicles will also be examined strictly.</p>



<p> Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Also see &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/joda-talab-to-be-renovated">Joda Talab to be renovated.</a></p>



<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-dc-meeting-news-19343801.html">Jagran</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/road-safety/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Joda Talab to be renovated</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/joda-talab-to-be-renovated</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/joda-talab-to-be-renovated#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 16:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chaibasa]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joda Talab]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=388</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Another good news for people of Chaibasa. First Jubilee Lake, then Dada-Dadi Park and now Joda Talab is going to be renovated and a park is going to be constructed around the lake. This Winter, the City Council is going to give us a gift for our morning walk in the cold weather. For this, &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/joda-talab-to-be-renovated" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Joda Talab to be renovated"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/HH_CHB05JAM_5_FEB_CBSA_P11_1518004037_1518004037.jpg" alt="Joda Talab, Chaibasa" class="wp-image-389" width="609" height="457" srcset="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/HH_CHB05JAM_5_FEB_CBSA_P11_1518004037_1518004037.jpg 480w, https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/HH_CHB05JAM_5_FEB_CBSA_P11_1518004037_1518004037-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 709px) 85vw, (max-width: 909px) 67vw, (max-width: 984px) 61vw, (max-width: 1362px) 45vw, 600px" /><figcaption>Joda Talab, Chaibasa</figcaption></figure>



<p>Another good news for people of Chaibasa.  First Jubilee Lake, then Dada-Dadi Park and now Joda Talab is going to be renovated and a park is going to be constructed around the lake.</p>



<p>This Winter, the City Council is going to give us a gift for our morning walk in the cold weather. For this, almost all the preparations have been done by the city council. This long-running project of the Chaibasa town, which is pending for several years could be taken up this year. But if it rains heavily in July then the work can stop because the city council will take one month for this process.</p>



<p>On June 18, the City Development Department Ranchi has transferred <strong> 6 Crore 13 lakh rupees</strong> to Chaibasa Nagar Parishad for the renovation and beautification of Joda Talab. But this money will take around a week to come into the account of the City Council as this amount will be deposited in the accounts of the City Council Chaibasa only after the required order and signature of the Deputy Commissioner. </p>



<p>Subsequently, the Municipal Council will issue tender for the restoration and beautification of Joda Talab. Overall, the restoration and beautification of the added pond will take one month to start. In the meantime, if it rains, then the pond will be filled with water and the contractor will have to stop the work. It will take at least 15 days to clean it.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<p>People will get many facilities in and around the pond.</p>



<p>Steel railing will be constructed around the pond. Stone boulder will be applied. A three meter leaf block will be laid. Grass and plantation will be done. The chair will be seated with the block. Two rounded stairs and one straight stair will be installed in the pond. A machine will be installed to filter the water the pond of the small pond so that the filtered water could be brought to the larger pond. ETP (Effect Treatment Plant) and CETP (Common Treatment Plant) will be installed. Three big fountains will be planted with lightning in the bigger pond. Street lights will be mounted around the pond. Besides this, dustbins will be installed to avoid dirt around the pond. The grass will be planted around the pond.</p>



<p>For a long time, the path of restoration and beautification of Joda Talab in the middle of Chaibasa city has become clear. For this, the City Development Department has transferred six crores and 13 lakh rupees to the bank account of City Council Chaibasa. Now a little government process is left, it will be completed soon and the tender will be done so that the work of restoration and beautification can be started.</p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-taalab-nirmaan-19326771.html">Jagran</a></p>



<p>Also see &#8211; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/dada-dadi-park-inaugurated-in-chaibasa">Dada Dadi Park in Chaibasa</a></p>



<p>

Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/joda-talab-to-be-renovated/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dada Dadi Park Inaugurated in Chaibasa</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/dada-dadi-park-inaugurated-in-chaibasa</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/dada-dadi-park-inaugurated-in-chaibasa#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 11:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Dada Dadi Park]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=383</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Dada-Dadi Park constructed by the city council for the cost of 95 lakh rupees was inaugurated on Wednesday. With the inauguration of the park, the elderly people living around here can roam in the park during morning and evening and get health benefits. Open gym and swings are built for children and fitness of youth. &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/dada-dadi-park-inaugurated-in-chaibasa" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Dada Dadi Park Inaugurated in Chaibasa"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img loading="lazy" width="650" height="487" src="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/19_06_2019-19chap23-c-2_19326938_21419.jpg" alt="Dada Dadi Park" class="wp-image-384" srcset="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/19_06_2019-19chap23-c-2_19326938_21419.jpg 650w, https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/19_06_2019-19chap23-c-2_19326938_21419-300x225.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 709px) 85vw, (max-width: 909px) 67vw, (max-width: 984px) 61vw, (max-width: 1362px) 45vw, 600px" /><figcaption>Dada Dadi Park</figcaption></figure>



<p>Dada-Dadi Park constructed by the city council for the cost of 95 lakh rupees was inaugurated on Wednesday. With the inauguration of the park, the elderly people living around here can roam in the park during morning and evening and get health benefits. Open gym and swings are built for children and fitness of youth. </p>



<p>Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal inaugurated the park. While inaugurating Dada-Dadi Park in front of Civil Surgeon Housing on Wednesday, He said that earlier this place used to contain a pile of dirt and garbages. It is a good initiative of the city council that its citizens have availed the benefits. It will be maintained by the city council but if local people also pay attention, the beauty of the park will be enriched. </p>



<p>On the occasion, Municipal Council President Mithilesh Kumar Thakur, Vice President Doma Miz, Sadar Sub-divisional Officer Paritosh Kumar Thakur, District Education Officer Pradeep Kumar Choubey, Executive Officer Abhay Kumar Jha, Provident Fund Officer Kamal Kumar Singh, Sage Vedant Khirwal, Babu of Artha Industries Pvt Ltd Apart from Bhattacharya the Ward Councilor was present.</p>



<p>Features of Dada Dadi Park &#8211; </p>



<p>length of the park is 650 Feet and width is 45 feet <br> There are 200 Bowled Light, 56 street light and 3 fountains</p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-dadai-dada-park-19326938.html">Jagran</a></p>



<p>Read More on this &#8211;  <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/03/park-in-front-of-civil-surgeon-house">Park in Gandhi Tola</a></p>



<p>

Follow us on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook&nbsp;</a>and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/dada-dadi-park-inaugurated-in-chaibasa/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ayushman Yojna in Private Hospitals</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/ayushman-yojna-in-private-hospitals</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/ayushman-yojna-in-private-hospitals#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 15:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorised]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Ayushman Yojna]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chaibasa]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.chaibasa.org/?p=378</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Golden cardholders from West Singhbhum district will now be able to get treatment of 150 additional diseases in the private hospital from Prime Minister Ayushman Yojna. Government of India has given exemption in the private hospital for the treatment of 150 diseases including HIV, Chikungunya, Dengue, Hernia. In the past, the above diseases were treated &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/ayushman-yojna-in-private-hospitals" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Ayushman Yojna in Private Hospitals"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img loading="lazy" width="650" height="400" src="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/2019_2largeimg04_Feb_2019_082443502.jpg" alt="Ayushman Yojna Logo" class="wp-image-380" srcset="https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/2019_2largeimg04_Feb_2019_082443502.jpg 650w, https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/2019_2largeimg04_Feb_2019_082443502-300x185.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 709px) 85vw, (max-width: 909px) 67vw, (max-width: 984px) 61vw, (max-width: 1362px) 45vw, 600px" /><figcaption>Ayushman Yojna</figcaption></figure>



<p>Golden cardholders from West Singhbhum district will now be able to get treatment of 150 additional diseases in the private hospital from Prime Minister Ayushman Yojna. Government of India has given exemption in the private hospital for the treatment of 150 diseases including HIV, Chikungunya, Dengue, Hernia.</p>



<p><br> In the past, the above diseases were treated in government hospitals only. About 12 thousand families of the district will get the benefit. At present, about 1350 diseases in the district are being treated with Ayushman Yojna. Of these, 1047 diseases were being treated in a private hospital. Under the scheme, only 203 types of diseases were being treated at the government hospital. </p>



<p><br> In the absence of facilities in government hospitals, the patient was not getting the treatment properly. The government has allowed 157 other diseases to be treated in private hospitals. Despite this, its 146 diseases will still be treated only in government hospitals.</p>



<p>Also see &#8211;  <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/rare-birds-found-in-chaibasa-chandmari-lake">Rare Birds in Chaibasa</a></p>



<p> Follow us on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Chaibasa.org">Facebook </a>and <a href="https://www.instagram.com/Chaibasa_org">Instagram</a></p>



<p>Source &#8211; <a href="https://www.prabhatkhabar.com/news/singhbhum-west/story/1293400.html">Prabhat Kabar</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2019/06/ayushman-yojna-in-private-hospitals/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
