<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<atom:link href="https://www.chaibasa.org/category/uncategorized/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<description>Chaibasa is a town and a municipality in West Singhbhum district in the state of Jharkhand, India.</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 18:48:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	

<image>
	<url>https://www.chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/cropped-abc1-3-32x32.jpg</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Chaibasa</title>
	<link>https://www.chaibasa.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Annual Sports Day celebration in St. Xavier&#8217;s</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/annual-sports-day-celebration-in-st-xaviers</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/annual-sports-day-celebration-in-st-xaviers#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chaibasa.org/2018/12/annual-sports-day-celebration-in-st-xaviers</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Annual Sports Day was organized on behalf of Saint Xavier&#8217;s English Medium School and Junior College on Wednesday at the Association Ground of Chaibasa. As the chief guest in the program, Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal, Dyasis head office in the special guest, Reverged Father of the Jamshedpur, Augustine Topon, the dignitary guest, SDPO of the &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/annual-sports-day-celebration-in-st-xaviers" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Annual Sports Day celebration in St. Xavier&#8217;s"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"></p>
<div class="separator" style="clear:both;text-align:center;"><a href="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/c4a6d-05_12_2018-5chap25-c-2_18718199_203729.jpg" style="margin-left:1em;margin-right:1em;"><img loading="lazy" border="0" data-original-height="346" data-original-width="650" height="340" src="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/c4a6d-05_12_2018-5chap25-c-2_18718199_203729.jpg?w=300" width="640" /></a></div>
<p>Annual Sports Day was organized on behalf of Saint Xavier&#8217;s English Medium School and Junior College on Wednesday at the Association Ground of Chaibasa. As the chief guest in the program, Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal, Dyasis head office in the special guest, Reverged Father of the Jamshedpur, Augustine Topon, the dignitary guest, SDPO of the district Amar Kumar Pandey was present. The program was inaugurated by the Deputy Commissioner. In order to make the program successful, the Deputy Commissioner remembered the days of his school while praising the Principal of the Vidyalaya, Sister Sheetal, teachers and parents. In addition, all children are encouraged to participate in any sport with interest. This will enable the children to succeed in all spheres of life. On the spot, the children got a lot of enthusiasm in the children&#8217;s ball ball, relay race, sack race, cock battle race, apple race. Children&#8217;s Dance Program was also organized for entertainment along with sports. In this class, children of class 2, 3, were presented saris, charming dance by children of dance dance and children of 7,8,9 by Pam-Pam Dance, Class 4,5,6 children. In the event, the Acura House Yellow Team was the Overall Champion.</p>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-sports-day-18718199.html" target="_blank">Jagran</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/annual-sports-day-celebration-in-st-xaviers/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Children celebrate Annual Function in Shikshayatan English School</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/children-celebrate-annual-function-in-shikshayatan-english-school</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/children-celebrate-annual-function-in-shikshayatan-english-school#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chaibasa.org/2018/12/children-celebrate-annual-function-in-shikshayatan-english-school</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Annual Festival of Education School of English was celebrated on Sunday with cultural programs. As the Chief Guest of the function, Dr. Ranjit Prasad, Director of Human Resources Development Institute, Chaibasa, was invited. Together with the special guest Federation of Jharkhand Chamber of Commerce Industries, Kolhan Vice President Vikas Mishra and President of West &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/children-celebrate-annual-function-in-shikshayatan-english-school" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Children celebrate Annual Function in Shikshayatan English School"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"></p>
<div class="separator" style="clear:both;text-align:center;"><a href="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/e95a6-asf.jpg" style="margin-left:1em;margin-right:1em;"><img loading="lazy" border="0" data-original-height="353" data-original-width="650" height="346" src="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/e95a6-asf.jpg?w=300" width="640" /></a></div>
<p>The Annual Festival of Education School of English was celebrated on Sunday with cultural programs. As the Chief Guest of the function, Dr. Ranjit Prasad, Director of Human Resources Development Institute, Chaibasa, was invited. Together with the special guest Federation of Jharkhand Chamber of Commerce Industries, Kolhan Vice President Vikas Mishra and President of West Kashmir Chamber of Commerce Industries Bajrang Lal Chirania and Chairman of Red Cross Society Kishor Prasad launched the lamp lighting program. The festival was started by the students of the school by presenting Saraswati Vandana and Saraswati Vandana dance. After that, pop dance was presented by the brothers of LKG, including Krishna Mahato, IS Kumar Nayak, Navneet Pradhan, Rohan Das, Gora Hasada, Shraddha Kesari, Kshaskar Kadali, Smriti, Jannavi Nayak etc.. After that, &#8220;Mere Papa&#8221; song was danced by the children. After that, Bihar&#8217;s dance music, Sambalpuri Dance of Odisha, Nagpuri Dance of Chota Nagpur and local Ho Dance etc. were staged.</p>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-annual-funcation-18707341.html" target="_blank">Jagran</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/children-celebrate-annual-function-in-shikshayatan-english-school/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Clean and Green Chaibasa Awareness Campaign</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/clean-and-green-chaibasa-awareness-campaign</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/clean-and-green-chaibasa-awareness-campaign#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Dec 2018 04:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chaibasa.org/2018/12/clean-and-green-chaibasa-awareness-campaign</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This dream will be incomplete until all of them are involved in making clean Chaibasa-green chaibasa. For this, Sanitation Awareness Campaign was started on Friday in the Rungta Marwari Secondary School on behalf of the Municipal Council and Pioneer Agency. On the spot, City Manager of the City Council, Akash, made people aware of drought &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/clean-and-green-chaibasa-awareness-campaign" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Clean and Green Chaibasa Awareness Campaign"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;">
<div class="separator" style="clear: both; text-align: center;"><a style="margin-left: 1em; margin-right: 1em;" href="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/5a9ef-xyz.jpg"><img loading="lazy" src="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/5a9ef-xyz.jpg?w=300" width="640" height="302" border="0" data-original-height="308" data-original-width="650" /></a></div>
<p>This dream will be incomplete until all of them are involved in making clean Chaibasa-green chaibasa. For this, Sanitation Awareness Campaign was started on Friday in the Rungta Marwari Secondary School on behalf of the Municipal Council and Pioneer Agency. On the spot, City Manager of the City Council, Akash, made people aware of drought waste and wet waste. He said that throwing garbage around the environment is polluted. Apart from this, the possibility of spreading various kinds of diseases is always maintained. Therefore, the people of the city council area put dry and wet garbage in the trains of the city council. Everyone should keep two buckets in their homes. Drained garbage in one and putting in a garbage in one and putting it in the cart. The city will also be clean and one day nobody can stop making the city clean chaibasa and green chaibasa. Provided it requires cooperation of all. Akash said that the waste is also made from this waste which works very fertile in the fields. If the waste manure is put into the farm, the crop of the field will be seen. In this campaign every section should be accompanied. For this work, all sections should be aware and come forward. Because this city belongs to all. Not only is the town council of the city. On the occasion, a large number of schoolchildren were present on the occasion including the Pioneer agency&#8217;s Atul, TMC&#8217;s friendliness, teacher Nirmal Chandra Tripathi.</p>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-cleaning-abhiyaan-18699695.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Jagran</a></p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/12/clean-and-green-chaibasa-awareness-campaign/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>One Day Vedic Jagaran Camp organised in DAV Chaibasa</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/one-day-vedic-jagaran-camp-organised-in-dav-chaibasa</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/one-day-vedic-jagaran-camp-organised-in-dav-chaibasa#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 16:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chaibasa762672159.wordpress.com/2018/11/27/one-day-vedic-jagaran-camp-organised-in-dav-chaibasa/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One day Vedic Jagaran Camp Arya Udbhopan was organized in Surajmall Jain DAV Public School Chaibasa. The camp was started with Prabhat fheri with the 11 Kundya Havan-Yagna. Dr. K. Srivastava, Regional Officer of Jharkhand Zone B &#38; F of DAV Public School was present as the Chief Guest. Dr. K. S. Srivastava said that &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/one-day-vedic-jagaran-camp-organised-in-dav-chaibasa" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "One Day Vedic Jagaran Camp organised in DAV Chaibasa"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><img alt="à¤¡à¥à¤à¤µà¥ à¤¸à¥à¤à¥à¤² à¤¹à¤®à¤¾à¤°à¥ à¤®à¥à¤à¥à¤¦à¤¾ à¤à¤µà¤¶à¥à¤¯à¤à¤¤à¤¾ à¤à¥ à¤ªà¥à¤°à¥à¤¤à¤¿ : à¤¡à¥. à¤à¥à¤¸à¥ à¤¶à¥à¤°à¥à¤µà¤¾à¤¸à¥à¤¤à¤µ" src="https://www.jagranimages.com/images/26_11_2018-26chap1-c-2_18685664_235729.jpg" /></p>
<p>One day Vedic Jagaran Camp Arya Udbhopan was organized in Surajmall Jain DAV Public School Chaibasa. The camp was started with Prabhat fheri with the 11 Kundya Havan-Yagna. Dr. K. Srivastava, Regional Officer of Jharkhand Zone B &amp; F of DAV Public School was present as the Chief Guest. Dr. K. S. Srivastava said that the DAV School fulfills our current requirement. While expressing gratitude towards Nismore Sanand ND Grover, he appealed teachers to give suggestions in the interest of the school. Pandit Vasudev Shastri highlighted the importance of books on Maharishi Dayanand, the Satyam Prakash and Sanskar method books, through persuasive references. Swami Shraddhanand was the first person to receive the title of Mahatma from the title of Mahatma. While expressing the sentiments by the poetry text, Principal Line Kumari said that we assume the views of Maharishi Dayanand. Rishi sang and the presentation of the ten rules of the Arya Samaj was commendable. From the hymns, discourse and collective song dance, the camp got rainbow. Mmantji talked about children flying high Pandit Jagbandhu Shastri, Prakashananda and Ashutosh Shastri addressed the gathering. On this occasion SK Pathak, Pradnya Singh, SK Jha, TK Mishra, N Paisit, Anoop Kumar, LMC member Abhishek Dodarajka, Former Tata Institute of Technology BN Tudu and teachers were present on the occasion.</p>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-dav-school-fulfills-our-current-requirement-dr-kc-srivastava-18685664.html" target="_blank">Jagran</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/one-day-vedic-jagaran-camp-organised-in-dav-chaibasa/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pillai Hall of Chaibasa will appear in new colors</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/pillai-hall-of-chaibasa-will-appear-in-new-colors</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/pillai-hall-of-chaibasa-will-appear-in-new-colors#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 18:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chaibasa.org/2018/11/pillai-hall-of-chaibasa-will-appear-in-new-colors</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Due worship was done on behalf of SR Rungta Group on Friday about the grand restoration of Pillai Hall at a cost of 20 million rupees. On this occasion, BJP state president Sahbum MP Laxman Giluva, Chaibasa Sadar JMM MLA Deepak Biruva, deputy commissioner Arva Rajkamal, deputy chairperson of minority commission Ashok Shardangi and renowned &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/pillai-hall-of-chaibasa-will-appear-in-new-colors" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Pillai Hall of Chaibasa will appear in new colors"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><a href="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/9f86f-46495585_1616482538452234_3961474759186710528_n.jpg" style="margin-left:1em;margin-right:1em;text-align:center;"><img loading="lazy" border="0" data-original-height="540" data-original-width="960" height="360" src="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/9f86f-46495585_1616482538452234_3961474759186710528_n.jpg?w=300" width="640" /></a><br />Due worship was done on behalf of SR Rungta Group on Friday about the grand restoration of Pillai Hall at a cost of 20 million rupees. On this occasion, BJP state president Sahbum MP Laxman Giluva, Chaibasa Sadar JMM MLA Deepak Biruva, deputy commissioner Arva Rajkamal, deputy chairperson of minority commission Ashok Shardangi and renowned industrialist Mukund Rungta were present on the occasion. The program was first welcomed by Mukund Rungta by giving a bouquet of guests. After this, all the attendees prayed to God for the beauty of Pillai Hall. Speaking on the occasion, MP Laxman Giluva addressed the people saying that Pillai Hall of Chaibasa town was very old. There was a dire need for its restoration It is a matter of great joy that the restoration work is done by the SR Rungta Group. Because in this situation, political, non-political, social and other different programs are organized. The big identity for the city of Chaibasa is Pillai Hall. MLA Deepak Birua congratulated Mukund Rungta, Director of SR Rungta Group for the restoration of Pillai Hall. That is the oldest Pillai Hall in the city. Its scarcity was running for a long time. Now it will go a lot again on this day and there is a great news for the people of Chaibasa. Deputy Commissioner Arwa Rajkamal said that the budget for the first 80 lakhs was built for the restoration of Pillai Hall, but due to its lack of beauty, this budget has been increased to two crore and 15 lakhs. Mukund Rungta, director, industrialist and social worker, SR Rungta Group said that the renovation of Pillai Hall will be completed in 8 to 9 months. Twenty million and 15 million budgets have been made for the budget. If a little too much will be seen then the SR Rungta Group will not go back. The cultural program of August 15 will be done in this AC Auditorium Hall in 2019. On the occasion, industrialist co-social worker Raj Kumar Shah, Sanjay Pandey, BJP district president Dinesh Chandra Nandi, city president Vikas Kumar Sharma, Chaibasa Chamber president Nitin Prakash, FJCCI&#8217;s Coalhan Vice-Chairman Vikas Chandra Mishra, Sanjay Akhara, Giridhi Parik, Suresh Poddar, Baljeet Singh Khokhar, Kolhan Chamber President Bajrang Lal Chiraniya, Senior Advocate VN Pandey, Niranjan Prasad Sau, Ures Co, Narayan Padia, Trishanu Rai, Balram Sultania and many others attended the event.</p>
<p></p>
<div class="separator" style="clear:both;text-align:center;"></div>
<p></p>
<div class="separator" style="clear:both;text-align:center;"><a href="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/5d847-46506211_1616482661785555_5329007997093937152_n.jpg" style="margin-left:1em;margin-right:1em;"><img loading="lazy" border="0" data-original-height="540" data-original-width="960" height="360" src="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/5d847-46506211_1616482661785555_5329007997093937152_n.jpg?w=300" width="640" /></a></div>
<p></p>
<div class="separator" style="clear:both;text-align:center;"><a href="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/7f568-46774695_1616482618452226_7230540969953722368_n.jpg" style="margin-left:1em;margin-right:1em;"><img loading="lazy" border="0" data-original-height="540" data-original-width="960" height="360" src="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/7f568-46774695_1616482618452226_7230540969953722368_n.jpg?w=300" width="640" /></a></div>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-chaibasa-news-18673534.html" target="_blank">Jagran</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/pillai-hall-of-chaibasa-will-appear-in-new-colors/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chaibasa ITI will take employment fair</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/chaibasa-iti-will-take-employment-fair</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/chaibasa-iti-will-take-employment-fair#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chaibasa762672159.wordpress.com/2018/11/23/chaibasa-iti-will-take-employment-fair/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The recruitment camp cum employment fair is being organized by the District Planning Department under the aegis of Labor Planning and Training Department under the aegis of the Government of Jharkhand on 24th November at the Government ITI campus. Applications for 1600 posts have been invited by Sabari Group, Bangalore in the said recruitment camp &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/chaibasa-iti-will-take-employment-fair" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Chaibasa ITI will take employment fair"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;">The recruitment camp cum employment fair is being organized by the District Planning Department under the aegis of Labor Planning and Training Department under the aegis of the Government of Jharkhand on 24th November at the Government ITI campus. Applications for 1600 posts have been invited by Sabari Group, Bangalore in the said recruitment camp cum employment fair. Eligible beneficiaries of the District whose qualifications are Diploma, ITI 10th, 12th pass, Diploma in Electronics and Communication, they can participate in this recruitment camp cum employment fair. Selected beneficiaries will be provided employment at monthly salary of 13,000 to 15000 rupees in Chennai and Bengaluru.</p>
<p>District Planning Officer Ravi Kumar informed that all selected candidates will be provided with PF, ESI as well as transportation facilities provided by Sabri Group, Bangalore. All the original certificates and one shadow copy of the above recruitment camp, passport size photograph, original Vocational Registration card of the scheme, Aadhar card, while applying for registration in the Jharkhand any planning agency, qualified and interested candidate who is not already registered in the planning. And with our BioData on 24th November at 10am at the ITI campus, this campus recruitment camp is being organized in Chaibasa. The benefits may take.</p>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-rojgaar-mela-18668841.html" target="_blank">Jagran</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/chaibasa-iti-will-take-employment-fair/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Birsa Jayanti</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/birsa-jayanti</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/birsa-jayanti#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://chaibasa.org/2018/11/birsa-jayanti</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Birsa Munda, freedom fighter in British era, is remembered for bringing a tribal revolution in India. He belonged to the Munda tribe, most common in Jharkhand, Odisha, West Bengal and parts of Bihar, Chhattisgarh, Arunachal Pradesh, Tripura and Madhya Pradesh. The group is one of India&#8217;s largest scheduled tribes. Birsa Munda was born on November &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/birsa-jayanti" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Birsa Jayanti"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;"><span>Birsa Munda, freedom fighter in British era, is remembered for bringing a tribal revolution in India. He belonged to the Munda tribe, most common in Jharkhand, Odisha, West Bengal and parts of Bihar, Chhattisgarh, Arunachal Pradesh, Tripura and Madhya Pradesh. The group is one of India&#8217;s largest scheduled tribes. Birsa Munda was born on November 15, 1875 and his birthday is celebrated as Birsa Munda Jayanti. </span></p>
<div class="separator" style="clear:both;text-align:center;"><a href="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/5df12-birsa1.jpg" style="margin-left:1em;margin-right:1em;"><img loading="lazy" border="0" data-original-height="756" data-original-width="564" height="320" src="http://chaibasa.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/12/5df12-birsa1.jpg?w=224" width="238" /></a></div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/birsa-jayanti/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Friendship Cricket Match of teachers in Chaibasa on 15th</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/friendship-cricket-match-of-teachers-in-chaibasa-on-15th</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/friendship-cricket-match-of-teachers-in-chaibasa-on-15th#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 18:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chaibasa762672159.wordpress.com/2018/11/11/friendship-cricket-match-of-teachers-in-chaibasa-on-15th/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On 15th November, a Friendship Cricket match has been organized between teachers of primary vs. middle and middle school teachers of West Bank in Birsa Munda Cricket Stadium ground on the occasion of Lord Birsa Munda&#8217;s birth anniversary and Jharkhand State Foundation Day. To participate in the said match, the primary school teachers&#8217; team will &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/friendship-cricket-match-of-teachers-in-chaibasa-on-15th" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Friendship Cricket Match of teachers in Chaibasa on 15th"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;">On 15th November, a Friendship Cricket match has been organized between teachers of primary vs. middle and middle school teachers of West Bank in Birsa Munda Cricket Stadium ground on the occasion of Lord Birsa Munda&#8217;s birth anniversary and Jharkhand State Foundation Day.</p>
<p>To participate in the said match, the primary school teachers&#8217; team will be selected in the Birsa Munda Cricket Stadium ground on Wednesday. It is mandatory for the participating teachers to bring their teacher identity card with them. The selection committee formed by the District Cricket Association will be selected by both teams. The players of both the selected teams will report on the Birsa Munda Cricket Stadium ground at 10 am on November 15. The District Education Officer and District Superintendent of Police will jointly inaugurate the match organized by the Department of District Education and Literacy while the Deputy Commissioner will be rewarded as a Chief Guest in the closing ceremony.</p>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-friendship-of-teachers-in-chaibasa-cricket-match15-18623226.html" target="_blank">Jagran</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/11/friendship-cricket-match-of-teachers-in-chaibasa-on-15th/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Foundation laid for projects worth Rs 428cr in Chaibasa</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/foundation-laid-for-projects-worth-rs-428cr-in-chaibasa</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/foundation-laid-for-projects-worth-rs-428cr-in-chaibasa#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 16:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chaibasa762672159.wordpress.com/2018/10/29/foundation-laid-for-projects-worth-rs-428cr-in-chaibasa/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Jharkhand Chief Minister Raghubar Das on Monday laid the foundation for various projects worth Rs 428 crore in Chaibasa, the district headquarter of mineral-rich West Singhbhum. While Rs 380 crore would be spent on eight water projects to provide drinking water in the rural belt of the district, the remaining amount would be spent on &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/foundation-laid-for-projects-worth-rs-428cr-in-chaibasa" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Foundation laid for projects worth Rs 428cr in Chaibasa"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;">
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Jharkhand Chief Minister Raghubar Das on Monday laid the foundation for various projects worth Rs 428 crore in Chaibasa, the district headquarter of mineral-rich West Singhbhum.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">While Rs 380 crore would be spent on eight water projects to provide drinking water in the rural belt of the district, the remaining amount would be spent on road construction in rural areas.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Regretting that the people of Chaibasa were forced to drink unsafe water even 70 years after independence, the chief minister said he had promised to provide drinking water through pipelines in each villages of the district.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">The foundation of water projects was a step in this direction, he said adding that economy of the rural pockets would improve if the infrastructure including road and electricity was improved.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Director of District Rural Development Agency (DRDA), Amit Kumar said the government has set a target to provide piped drinking water to all the villages of the district by 2022.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">The chief minister assured to provide electricity in each villages of the state by December 2018.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">The Detail Project Report of a proposed medical college in Chaibasa was ready and tender would be floated soon to ensure that the work of the 500-bed medical college-cum-hospital start in a month or two, he said.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Prime Minister Narendra Modi had laid the foundation of two medical college and hospital including the one in Koderma during his visit to the state last month.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Besides, the government has also decided to establish a school in Khuntipani block of West Singhbhum district on the lines of famous Netarhat school of Latehar district.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Prior to the foundation stone laying ceremony, Das also inaugurated a &#8220;Jubilee Park&#8221; surrounding a lake, which was renovated and developed by Tata Steel for Rs 10 crore in the township.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Addressing the gathering on the occasion, Das hailed Tata Steels role in making a difference to the lives of people living in and around its operational areas.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">Referring to the new projects, Das said a majority of them will be on water and road construction worth Rs 427.92 crore which was being spent from the District Mineral Fund.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;">&#8220;During my first visit to Chaibasa after becoming the chief minister of the state, I had promised the people here to change the face and fate of the township and the inauguration of the park was fulfilment of my commitment,&#8221; Das said.</span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;"><span style="font-size:large;"><br /></span></div>
<div style="text-align:left;">Source :- <a href="https://www.business-standard.com/article/pti-stories/foundation-laid-for-projects-worth-rs-428cr-in-chaibasa-118102901062_1.html" target="_blank">Business standard</a></div>
<div style="height:0;text-align:left;"></div>
<div style="height:0;text-align:left;"></div>
<div style="height:0;text-align:left;"></div>
<div style="height:0;text-align:left;"></div>
<div style="height:0;text-align:left;"></div>
<div style="height:0;text-align:left;"></div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/foundation-laid-for-projects-worth-rs-428cr-in-chaibasa/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Global Agri Food Summit in Chaibasa</title>
		<link>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/global-agri-food-summit-in-chaibasa</link>
					<comments>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/global-agri-food-summit-in-chaibasa#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 03:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://chaibasa762672159.wordpress.com/2018/10/28/global-agri-food-summit-in-chaibasa/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[For the successful organizing of the Global Agri Food Summit 2018 to be held on November 29 and 30, a meeting was held under the chairmanship of District Industries General Manager, Shanbhushan. For the successful conduct of the summit, meeting of the Chamber of Commerce Industry, association, food processing, and meeting with the entrepreneur. The &#8230; <a href="https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/global-agri-food-summit-in-chaibasa" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Global Agri Food Summit in Chaibasa"</span></a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div dir="ltr" style="text-align:left;">For the successful organizing of the Global Agri Food Summit 2018 to be held on November 29 and 30, a meeting was held under the chairmanship of District Industries General Manager, Shanbhushan. For the successful conduct of the summit, meeting of the Chamber of Commerce Industry, association, food processing, and meeting with the entrepreneur. The people of the agriculture and allied departments told that before the program road shows will be organized in the district. The provisions made by the State Government related to food processing by the General Manager were stated in the provisions of Jharkhand Food Processing 2018. District District Officer Rajendra Kishore, Project Director Spirit Pankaj Kumar, District Garden Officer Santosh Lakra and others were present.</p>
<p>Source :- <a href="https://www.jagran.com/jharkhand/west-singhbhum-29-and-30-will-be-the-global-agri-food-summit-in-chaibasa-18576765.html" target="_blank">Jagran</a></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://www.chaibasa.org/2018/10/global-agri-food-summit-in-chaibasa/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
